Guide to the Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002, bulk 1951-2001 RL.10070
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal Files, 1949-2002; 6 boxes
  - Loft Papers, 1969-2002
    - 1984, Commemorative Cooper Square pamphlet (Box P3)
    - 1984, Sublet (Box P3)
    - 1984-1987 and undated, Gentrification issues (Box P3)
    - 1984-1988 and undated, Appliance owner's manuals (Box P3)
    - 1984-1991 and undated, Tenant newsletters and clippings (Box P3)
    - 1985, Cooper Square Committee – Carmen Barreto controversy (Box P3)
    - 1985, Lower East Side Joint Planning Council (Box P3)
    - 1985-1992 and undated, Sublet (Box P3)
    - 1986, Cooper Square Committee, Cooper Square Plan report (Box P4)
    - 1986-1987, Cooper Square Committee minutes (Box P4)
    - 1987 and undated, Remodeling (Box P4)
    - 1987-1989 and undated, Cooper Square Committee minutes and by-laws (Box P4)
    - 1988 and undated, "The Hole in the Wall" – outside building repairs (Box P4)
    - 1988 and undated, Windows (Box P4)
    - 1988-1990 and undated, Maintenance and improvements (Box P4)
    - 1988-1992 and undated, Cooper Square Committee minutes, 4 folders (Box P4)
    - 1989, Housing in Boston (Box P4)
    - 1989-1990, New York City auctions for commercial rental space (Box P4)
    - 1990, Cooper Square Committee, Thelma Burdick pamphlet (Box P4)
    - 1990, Electronic format only: Sublet agreement between Millett and Eda Smyth
      - file name Loft, 1990 May 19 (Disk019) (Box P4)
    - 1990 and undated, Housing Justice Campaign (Box P4)
    - 1991, Electronic format only: Letter to landmarks commission
      - file name Landmark, 1991 Feb. 24 (Disk019) (Box P4)
    - 1992 and undated, Neighborhood association politics – correspondence and notes (Box P4)
    - 1993, Renovations evidence for legal file (Box P4)
    - 1994, Bowery building directory (Box P4)
    - 1994 and undated, Cooper Square Committee and fight for the loft (Box P4)
    - 1997, Bowery Land Grab clipping and letters to the editor (Box P4)
    - Circa 1999, "Kate's History of the House She Lives In" (Box P4)
    - 2001, The Loft and 9/11 (Box P4)
    - 2002 and undated, Mailings (Box P4)
    - Undated, Notes – boxing in the windows (Box P4)
    - Undated, Petition for landmark designation for 305-7 Bowery (Box P4)
  - Other Personal Files, 1958-1990s
    - 1958, Academic job search, 1 of 2 folders (Box P4)
    - 1958, Academic job search, 2 of 2 folders (Box P5)
    - 1959-1960, Job search (Box P5)
    - 1967, Appointment book (Box P5)
    - 1967-1975 and undated, Address books, check receipts, and notes (Box P5)
    - Circa 1960s, Address book and notes (Box P5)
    - 1971-1984 and undated, Cars and insurance, 2 folders (Box P5)
    - 1972-1984 and undated, Cars (Box P5)
    - 1973 and undated, Calendar and notes (Box P5)
    - 1973-1974, Academic job search (Box P5)
    - 1974, Calendar and notes (Box P5)
    - 1977-1982 and undated, "FBI Follies" - Anti-FBI literature and correspondence on FBI/CIA records (Box P5)
    - 1979-1993 and undated, "FBI Follies" – Fund for Open Information and Accountability (FOIA), Political Rights Defense Fund, and correspondence (Box P5)
    - 1979, Notes – "What You Need To Do To Get Your Life in Order" (Box P5)
    - Circa 1970s, Address book (Box P5)
    - 1980, Accident and home insurance (Box P6)
    - 1982 and undated, Notes and manuscript "Living Alone" (Box P6)
    - 1984, "Genealogical and Historical Sketch" of Millett name, pamphlet (Box P6)
    - 1986-1991 and undated, Notes – addresses, 3 folders (Box P6)
    - 1986-1994 and undated, Holiday cards (Box P6)
    - Circa 1980s, "FBI Follies" - FOIA (Box P6)
    - 1988-1990, Electronic format only: Addresses and phone numbers
      - Alan Wilson address, file name Address.tut, 1990 May 13 (Disk018) (Box P6)
      - A few addresses, file name Clients.wkb, 1990 May 13 (Disk018) (Box P6)
      - Robin Pierce address, file names Customer.wkb and Address.bk! 1990 May 13 (Disk018) (Box P6)
      - Robin Pierce address, file name Address.wkb, 1990 May 8 (Disk018) (Box P6)
      - Frequently called phone numbers, file name Frphone, 1990 Sept. 22 (Disk019) (Box P6)
    - 1990, Electronic format only: Letter about a living will
      - file name Lifewill, 1990 Mar. 28 (Disk019) (Box P6)
    - 1991 and undated, Bread the Cat
      - A few sentences about Millett's cat, file name Bread, 1990 May 28 (Disk018) (Box P6)
    - 1993, Curriculum vita (Box P6)
    - 1994, Will and estate planning correspondence (Box P6)
    - 1997 and undated, Academic job search (Box P6)
    - Circa 1998, Curriculum vita (Box P6)
    - 1998, Jury duty paperwork (Box P6)
    - 1990s, Curriculum vitae (Box P6)
    - Undated, Blank note cards (Box P6)
    - Undated, To–do lists (Box P6)
    - Undated, Voting card, New York City (Box P6)
- Documentary Film: Three Lives (1970), 1970-1991 and undated; 2 boxes
  Three Lives was a documentary film produced by Millett and featuring Millett's sister Mallory Millett-Jones, Lillian Shreve, and Robin Mide. The film led to a lawsuit over the distribution of profits among the various women involved.
  The series consists of production material, distribution and financial records, and some legal correspondence. Undated production material are placed first, followed by other records in chronological order. A 16mm audio recording from the film production is located in the Audiovisual Materials Series. A viewing copy of the film is not currently available.
  - Undated Production Material:
    - Shooting notes and partial transcripts, undated (Box TL1)
    - Lillian – transcripts and editing, undated, 3 folders (Box TL1)
    - Lillian notes and editing, undated (Box TL1)
    - Mallory – transcripts and editing, undated, 4 folders (Box TL1)
    - Mallory – complete carbons, undated (Box TL1)
    - Robin – transcripts and editing, undated, 6 folders (Box TL1)
    - "Universal Rap," typescript dialogue between three women, undated (Box TL1)
  - Material by Date:
    - 1970 and undated, Equipment contracts (Box TL1)
    - 1970-1971 and undated, Production – shooting notes and correspondence (Box TL1)
    - 1970-1972 and undated, Partnership agreement, notes, and correspondence (Box TL1)
    - 1970-1973 and undated, Financial records (Box TL1)
    - 1971 and undated, Cue and credit sheets (Box TL1)
    - 1971 and undated, Notes and business correspondence (Box TL1)
    - 1971-1972 and undated, Reviews and flyers (Box TL1)
    - 1972, Women and Film journal with Three Lives review (Box TL2)
    - 1972, Festival of Women's Films poster (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1973, Flyers (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1973, Impact Films catalogs (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1973, Women's Cinema film festival catalog, National Film Theatre, London (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1973 and undated, Legal and financial papers (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1973 and undated, Three Lives and new movie finances (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1973-1989 and undated, Financial correspondence (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1974, New York Magazine clipping and Millett's response (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1980, Bank statements (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1980, German poster (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1980, 1990-1991 and undated, German release correspondence (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1981 and undated, French distribution notes (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1981-1983 and undated, Correspondence (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1988-1989 and undated, CUNY-TV screening (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - 1991 and undated, Whitney Museum screening (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - Undated, Address sheet (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - Undated, Advertisement (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - Undated, Interview with Millett, edited typescript (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - Undated, "The Making of Three Lives typescript (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - Undated, "Notes on the Making of Three Lives" article (Oversize-folder OS-2)
    - Undated, Photo of Kate Millett at Three Lives reception (Oversize-folder OS-2)
- Clippings, 1970s-1980 and undated; 3 boxes
  Newspaper and magazine clippings covering Millett's 1979 visit to and expulsion from Iran, Iranian feminism, and the Iranian political situation during that period. A wide spectrum of American, French, and (to a lesser extent) Persian-language media is included. A second focus of the series is media coverage of Millett's activities and projects, especially for the 1970s. Other clippings are related to Millett's wide-ranging personal and professional interests, particularly prison reform and the status of women's rights around the world. A small amount of correspondence and other material is intermixed with the clippings. There are also a number of full issues of activist publications and newsletters.
  In most cases, files in this series are arranged in original order, and have been left undated unless Millett's original folder title included a date range. There are few clippings from the 1980s. The series is in alphabetical order. Iran clippings are placed last, and are unorganized. Substantial numbers of clippings can be also found in the Subject Files and the Writings and Speeches Series.
  - Art clippings (Box CL1)
  - "Art" (Box CL1)
  - Baby M/surrogate motherhood (Box CL1)
  - Books (Box CL1)
  - California – Sacramento (Box CL1)
  - Clippings, 4 folders (Box CL1)
  - Feminism (Box CL1)
  - Interesting, 3 folders (Box CL1)
  - Yayoi Kusama (Box CL1)
  - Naked Ladies exhibit and interviews, 1977 (Box CL1)
  - National Forum for Women (Box CL1)
  - National Women's Conference, 1977 (Box CL1)
  - Press – engagements (Box CL1)
  - Press – general (Box CL1)
  - Reviews (Box CL1)
  - Sexual Harassment (Box CL1)
  - Sexual Politics, 1970, 1 of 2 folders (Box CL1)
  - Sexual Politics, 1970, 2 of 2 folders (Box CL2)
  - La Vie En Rose, 1980 Sept.-Nov. (Box CL2)
  - Kristen Vigard [Millett's niece] (Box CL2)
  - Iran, 1-17 of 23 folders (Box CL2)
  - Iran, 18-23 of 23 folders (Box CL3)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2000; 15 Linear Feet 22 boxes containing 458 items.
  The bulk of the series consists of audio recordings, chiefly on audiocassette, of Millett's public appearances, lectures, and interviews, and audio recordings of private conversations and social events involving Millett. The years 1979 and 1980 are particularly well represented. Millett made recordings almost daily during and after her 1979 visit to Iran and during the late summer of 1980. There are also audio recordings of Millett's mother and other family members, oral interviews for Millett's research on torture, and dictated drafts of A.D. and The Loony-Bin Trip. Early video recordings include lectures by Millett and Millett's readings of Anais Nin.
  Original audiovisual media is closed to use; access copies may be requested in advance. Please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use these materials.
  - Iran Recordings, 1979-1982
    - 1979 Mar. 3, Kate and Tree and Sophie before Iran, 1979 March 3
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0001)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:43:23+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0001_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:34:47+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0001_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 4, Kate and Milli on phone before Iran, 1979 March 4
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0002)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:48:01+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0002_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:52+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0002_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 5, Iran Sheraton Hotel - Sophie and Kate talk about day, 1979 March 5
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0003)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:22+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0003_01.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 6, In the car with Surmar/Kateh arrives to explain meeting, 1979 March 6
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0004)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:45:50+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0004_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:24:19+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0004_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 7, With Magi in car to unknown apt./Magi and Reswah, 1979 March 7
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0005)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:21+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0005_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:20+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0005_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 8, Teheran, Mass meeting, palace justice, 1979 March 8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0006)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:33:53+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0006_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:33:50+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0006_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 10, Kateh, 1979 March 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0007)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:19+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0007_01.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 10, Hotel interview, 1979 March 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0008)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:31:43+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0008_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:31:46+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0008_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 11, First press conference, 1979 March 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0009)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:48:41+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0009_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:20+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0009_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 11, First press conference, 1979 March 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0010)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:50:41+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0010_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:51:02+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0010_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 11-12, 1st min. March 11/Demo. Tehran Univ., 1979 March 11-12
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0011)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:27+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0011_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:48:07+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0011_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 12, March in streets, Tehran Univ. to Freedom Sq., 1979 March 12
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0012)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:50:58+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0012_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:33:28+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0012_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 12, March in streets, Tehran Univ. to Freedom Sq., 1979 March 12
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0013)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:18+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0013_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:20+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0013_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 13, Lunch with Iranian Italian women/Interview, 1979 March 13
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0014)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:50:47+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0014_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:50:09+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0014_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 13, Lunch with Italian Iranian lady/TV Demo, 1979 March 13
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0015)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:20+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0015_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:21+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0015_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 13, TV Demo, 1979 March 13
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0016)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:46:59+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0016_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:46:10+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0016_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 13, Meeting 2nd tape/Phones and Sophie and Kate, 1979 March 13
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0017)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:48:26+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0017_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:21+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0017_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 15, 1979 March 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0018)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:03:05+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0018_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:05:41+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0018_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 15, 1979 March 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0019)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:02:46+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0019_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:02:47+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0019_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 15, Expulsion, 1979 March 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0020)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:51:58+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0020_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:53:03+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0020_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 15, Expulsion, 1979 March 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0021)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:18+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0021_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:18+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0021_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 16, Kate and Sophie in hotel room before hearing ABC tape of press conf., 1979 March 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0022)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:46+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0022_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:47:19+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0022_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 16, Kate's statement from ABC/Me and Sophie in room, 1979 March 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0023)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:46:34+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0023_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:46:34+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0023_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 16, Expulsion press conference [may be damaged], 1979 March 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0024)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:03:26+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0024_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:41:40+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0024_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 19, Paris, People Magazine, 1979 March 19
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0025)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:31:05+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0025_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:31:05+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0025_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 19, Paris, People Magazine, 1979 March 19
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0026)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:32:37+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0026_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:33:02+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0026_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 22, Press conference, Paris, 1979 March 22
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0027)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:01:39+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0027_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:01:39+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0027_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 22, Press conference, Paris, 1979 March 22
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0028)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:49:18+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0028_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:48:35+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0028_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 22, Press conference, Paris, little machine, 1979 March 22
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0029)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:08:14+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0029_01.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 23, End of Paris interviews at Stock, 1979 March 23
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0030)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:03:35+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0030_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:13:52+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0030_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 24, Rome/Homecoming, 1979 March 24
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0031)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:46:53+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0031_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:31:31+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0031_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 25, Binghampton, 1979 March 25
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0032)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:02:28+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0032_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:01:32+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0032_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 25-26, NY press conf and end of Binghampton, 1979 March 25-26
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0033)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T01:01:39+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0033_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:46:19+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0033_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 26, Press conference release, 1979 March 26
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0034)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:03:26+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0034_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file, 1899-12-31T00:23:20+00:00 (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0034_02.wav)
    - 1979 Mar. 27, ABC Good Morning America TV interview, 1979 March 27
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0035)